Narrator: 5A
M: a scientist
a doctor
sometimes
usually
I’m not hungry.
early
healthy
traditional
important
different
favourite
in a café
at home
at work
soup
green tea
toast
a lot of
Narrator: 5B
M: a writer
a taxi driver
a British company
a flight
traffic
a gate
at university
at school
Do you want fish or pasta?
How’s your pasta?
I need to go to the toilet.
What time do we arrive?
Keep the change.
Can I see your passport and boarding pass, please?
What a nice surprise!
Narrator: 6A
F: What does she do?
Where does he work?
She’s a journalist.
She doesn’t wear glasses.
Her hair’s blonde.
He’s married to Laura.
Great to see you.
intelligent
How sad!
I love your shoes.
a barman
a banker
customers
dishes
a multinational company
meetings
Why? Because…
Narrator: 6B
M: Are you a morning person?
What time do you get up?
At eight o’clock.
He gets up at about 9.30.
feel tired
on the way to work
after work
every morning
then
a tour guide
an apartment
the subway
an omelette
It’s delicious.